[RAFIKI]
It's time to tell you a story.
A story of a cub not much bigger than you.
[TIMON]
So, just to be clear,
we are not in this story?
[PUMBA]
There's a lot of stories with all of us!
Tell one of those!
[RAFIKI]
Long before, they became legends...
Mufasa and the prince who would come to be known as Scar,
[RAFIKI]
became brothers.
[TAKA]
Hello, what's your name?
[MUFASA]
Mufasa
[ESHE]
I told you to wait for me!
[TAKA]
We can't just leave him here!
[ESHE]
Rules are rules, Taka!
The king will never accept a stray!
[MUFASA]
I am not a stray..
I am just.. lost
[MUSIC] 🎵🎵
[OBASI]
We do not associate with outsiders
Taka is the future king.
We must protect the bloodline.
[TAKA]
But dad, I saved his life!
[MUSIC] 🎵🎵